http://www.bankrollsports.com/privacy-policy.shtml

2019 Superbowl Odds
BCS National Champ.
Bankroll Sports Handicapping Website Company Privacy Policy
Our company privacy policy for the Bankroll Sports Handicapping website is as follows:
Bankroll Sports Handicapping values your privacy and we agree to keep all forms of your visitor & customer information 100% private. We respect our visitors' personal information and we choose to behave ethically in regards to their privacy.
We DO NOT and WILL NOT take your visitor information and release this information to any other company or service of any kind. We DO NOT and will never sell your information to any other sports handicapping service, online sportsbook, or sports betting related website for any reason (including monetary gain). This includes all information that that is either automatically collected by our servers, submitted by you for registration to our services, or submitted by you in order
to receive our free picks and promotional newsletters.
All of your information will remain private.
As with majority of internet website's, our server recognizes your browser's IP address which is linked to your network domain name. This information IS NOT and WILL NOT be released. This information will also be discarded from our server records in time. Our servers do not automatically collect any other visitor information that is not agreed upon by you.
In regards to ad servers & pop-ups: We DO NOT and WILL NOT take part in any ad servers or third-party pop-up programs that will show ads unrelated to our service. We will never take part in any program or ad server that could result in harm to your browser or local machine.
In regards to cookies: We DO NOT and WILL NOT install or use any third-party or in-house tracking cookies. We DO NOT and WILL NOT partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.
We do not send spam or unsolicited email messages. If you have received a free picks or promotional email from us in the past and wish to not wish to receive any mailings from us, you can remove your email address by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our mailers. We at Bankroll Sports Handicapping respect your wishes not to receive our newsletters.
If you received any unwanted email from us and do not wish to receive any mail from us at all, you can reply to the unwanted email and let us know. We will always agree never to send you any email at your request.
If you supplied us with your personal information when completing a purchase; which includes your mailing address, phone number, or credit card number, this information is not stored in our databases or in-house records and will not be used for any purpose other then the validation of that order.
Occasionally, we may make changes to this privacy policy. If our privacy practices change in the future, we will post these changes on this page. If you would like us to notify you of any changes to our privacy policy, you can contact us and request this notification using our contact form.
Visitors and customers can contact us if they have any questions about our company privacy policy by contacting us using our contact form.
If for any reason you feel that we are not abiding by the policy outlined on this page, you can contact us by using the contact form to let us know.
(Thursday, Friday, Saturday)
Premium Service Releases
100% Free of Charge!!
10% Back (on ALL BETS)
25% Bonus + 10% Cash Back
Our Sportsbook Review
Sport Bet Sportsbook
100% Match Play Bonus
Gradual Release! No Rollovers!
Get Some of The Best Signup Bonus Offers Along With Other Sportsbook Promocodes & Deals From Bankroll Sports by Visiting Our Review Pages!
Higher Limit Players Looking For High Limit Sportsbooks
Follow Our Free Sports Picks on Your Favorite Social Pages
If You Enjoy This Site, Please Like Us & Share Us on Your Favorite Social Networks!
Follow @BankrollSports
Today's Service Report
Exclusive 100% Sports Betting
Bonus @ Bookmaker Sportsbook
© Copyright 2008: Accelerated Sports Inc. - Bankroll Free Sports Picks & Handicapping Service & Information.
All Information on this site is property of Accelerated Inc. - © DMCA Copyright Laws will be strictly enforced.
Bankroll Sports Complete Sitewide Sitemap Listings: HTML Map Page 1 -
HTML Page 2 - RSS Map
